{
    "id": "f252a80ed31645948dd68b42e53c3827",
    "title": "Rewrite without get",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d963c2bac7ce4d7dbd7a1b935b05563a",
            "title": "Rewrite Without Get",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I (got) three hundred dollars last week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "acquired",
                        "gathered",
                        "earned"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I (got) a letter from my mother this morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "earned",
                        "received",
                        "acquired"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you come and (get) me from the station when I arrive?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "bring",
                        "fetch",
                        "take"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I didnâ€™t (get) the joke.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "acquire",
                        "find",
                        "understand"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "In the first half, the striker (got) a goal.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "earned",
                        "collected",
                        "scored"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "While studying in Sydney, Rahul (got) a strong Australian accent.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "gathered",
                        "earned",
                        "acquired"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The mother (got) the child to drink some of the milk.",
                    "description": "After made the infinitive is used without to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "coaxed",
                        "fetched",
                        "made"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "During the trip, many children (got) ill.",
                    "description": "Either fell or became is possible here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "fell",
                        "became",
                        "turned"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Luckily we (got) the last bus.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "caught",
                        "gained",
                        "collected"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They (got) a stay from the High Court.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "earned",
                        "collected",
                        "obtained"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}